const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '383 + 289 =', answer: '672', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '246 + 179 =', answer: '425', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '327 + 186 =', answer: '513', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '258 + 163 =', answer: '421', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '432 + 187 =', answer: '619', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '454 + 269 =', answer: '723', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '415 + 278 =', answer: '693', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '198 + 135 =', answer: '333', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '487 + 398 =', answer: '885', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '495 + 428 =', answer: '923', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];